192 000 is what I earn every month with
my sources of income with incomes
ranging from as little as a thousand
dollars to upwards of two hundred
thousand dollars in this video I will be
a hundred percent transparent showing
you each of my sources of income with
bank statements deposits everything I
will explain how I earn money with them
how I did it and how you can capitalize
off of them as well as I did I currently
have five sources of income the first
one is that apartment right there on the
fourth floors right it generates me
anywhere from about a thousand to a
thousand two hundred dollars a month and
it probably takes I'd say an hour out of
my time in the whole entire month I just
called attendant on the first like hey
is everything good is money good for the
first everything good hang up the phone
so it takes not much out of my time so I
generate the money through cash flow so
this is my first real estate property
and I did a grant card Loan Stop I put
20 down my monthly on it is about 1400
with interest and Association and I
rented out to the tenant for twenty four
hundred dollars a month after net profit
association fees and minor free is if
needed I'm left with about a thousand
dollars a month which is not much but I
pretty much got all the money that I
made and I reinvested into this to just
create passive income my second source
of income is back in the office and that
is from YouTube AdSense YouTube AdSense
generates anywhere from fifteen hundred
dollars a month to about two thousand
dollars a month this takes probably
about anywhere from three to four hours
a month because if I upload four videos
a month to record these videos for you
guys probably takes about an hour out of
my day so how do I make the money from
YouTube pretty much it's the ad right
before you watch this video you either
had to wait for the 15 second ad or you
had to click skip the ad so I get paid
pennies for every single ad but it adds
up for every hundred or a thousand views
or something like that so that is the
main way how I make money through my
YouTube which is just simple AdSense but
these ads fund the editors and everybody
behind the videos you know it just helps
the team because obviously running the
team to make these videos for you guys a
lot more expensive it just helps if you
haven't subscribed make sure you guys
hit that subscribe button and a brief
summary of how this started it was
actually the most random thing I was not
supposed to be on YouTube I would always
post my results on Instagram and then
people wanted to see longer versions of
how I how I did they wanted longer
explanations how I made the money that I
made and Instagram only let me do videos
for about a minute so I'm like you know
what I'm just gonna do a 15 20 minute 15
20 minute video and just upload it on
YouTube so people can watch the whole
thing and they can learn a lot more and
the feedback on YouTube was crazy
because it was a lot more content so
people can consume so I'm like you know
what I'm just gonna keep this YouTube
thing going and then it's grown to what
it is today which is totally insane
that's why I'm so grateful for the
community that has been built my third
source of income is my educational
business swing trading lab which I teach
you guys my set and forget strategy my
education of business really does vary
from 20 000 to about thirty thousand
dollars a month because I don't have it
available all the time I haven't had my
course available for a little over three
months so if you were to kind of added
up through the whole entire year I kind
of came to that average so I'd say any
words from twenty thousand to thirty
thousand if you were to spread it out
through the whole entire year to make
this it probably takes me anywhere from
two to three hours every single day
because every single morning I you know
send out the trades what I'm looking at
I get into the Discord I talk to the
guys and then on top of that on the
weekends I break down every single trade
that I get into to the whole entire
community so it can vary anywhere from
two to three hours a day take Saturdays
off and then on Sunday we are back at it
so the way the money is made with this
business is I offer an educational
service where I teach you how to trade
just like me so one-time payment you get
lifetime access to my educational videos
and lifetime access to my mentorship
meaning that every single week I am
guiding you to the markets and the
things that I'm going to be doing into
the week ahead and the way this started
it wasn't intentional again I just
started posting my results on social
media I was just showing people what I
did and then the demand was insane
people just couldn't believe that the
sniper entries that I was getting they
wanted to learn how I did it and then I
was doing it for free I had a free
telegram I had free videos on YouTube
free Instagram like everything free and
then I realized that I was doing so many
things for free that a lot of people
weren't respecting my time so I'm like
you know what I only want to work with
serious people people and instead of me
just doing it out there every single day
just forcing it I'm just going to make
all these recorded videos so you can
just go see it one time and that's it so
that's where I came up with swing
training lab where I teach you my set
and forget strategy my fourth source of
income is my small trading account so
this is very interesting because they
can make anywhere from fifteen thousand
dollars to upwards of twenty thousand
dollars in order for me to generate this
it could take anywhere from an hour to
two hours a day just come into the
markets either an hour during New York
or an hour during London that's pretty
much it I just wait for my Trade Center
to hit and that's it the way that I make
this money is I essentially take my
trading account and I risk a certain
percentage of it and I take it on a high
probability trade setup so whenever a
trade that has all of my confluences met
and I consider it to have a great risk
reward which is a minimum of a one to
two I then take the trade and the way
this came about is where a lot of people
want to know is how did you get the
money to have those accounts on your
small trading account how do you get the
account to make that and then truthfully
in order for you to get the money is you
have to be consistent and you have to
stick to your trading plan you have to
grow your account and honestly I did
some high risk trading at the beginning
my account grew and I managed to stay
with it a lot of Traders they can flip
accounts but then they don't know how to
stay with us so I grew my account over
time by just trading getting payouts and
not blowing the money I just kept
accumulating the account to where now I
can risk a certain percentage of it
where it gives me my returns on my
investment before I continue with my
last and biggest source of income I
would like to share with you other
sources of income that are not quite
stable especially because they're not
businesses they're just things that I
just throw money at and I see what
happens and the main reason is because
if I don't give something a hundred
percent I don't expect anything out of
it so these are just things that I kind
of dabble around with the first one
being affiliation with Brokers so what I
do is I just tell you what broker I use
and you basically sign up with the link
below and then if you sign up with the
link below I get paid per lot on the
trade that you take and with this I can
make anywhere from 1000 1000 to 2000 a
month I've had highs of three thousand
dollars a month however it's not stable
because one I think people like funding
companies better and two uh if you don't
sign up under my link below then I don't
get any conversation per law or trade
that you take so this way is why I don't
see a stable like the broker that I use
in the description below and if you
don't sign up with that link and you
just go on to the broker that I use and
you use it without using the link I
don't get benefits with it so that's why
I wouldn't consider this a source of
income but if you guys do want to know
what broker I use it's just in the
description below so the next one is
venture capitalist basically what I do
is I have friends that they have
businesses or money they want to throw
at I'm like you know what bro here's
some money I just need 15 back on the
money that I give you and as of right
now I've generated zero dollars for this
so all of the money that I gave to my
friends hasn't gone well and I've gotten
nothing back from it and this is not
stable because I don't think these guys
it's not their money and they see me as
their friend and like yo Alex just
prints money all day trading he could
just give me ten thousand dollars and
doesn't matter they don't they don't
respect the money this same or they
don't give it 100 so that's why I don't
consider this a source of income not
only because I've lost all of the money
that I've given these guys but because
they don't take it seriously the next
one would be cryptos what I do here is I
literally just buy a crypto so I don't
forget this has made me anywhere from
twenty thousand to sixty thousand
dollars a month and however I don't
really consider it a source of income
because I see it like as an investment
right I I can't depend on this a month
and it's not a guaranteed because you
guys are seeing the swings of cryptos
they have big highs and they have big
lows so I would just consider it
something you could throw money at it
and then when you make money you make
money and you run with it but don't
consider it a source of income every
single day because if you just plan to
hold crypto forever you only make the
money once you hit the withdraw button
but I will soon be buying a lots of
Bitcoin and a lot of ethereum so stay
tuned to that the last one that I
definitely don't consider assistive
income is poker so what I do with poker
is I basically just use it as a form to
network I just play with the boys and
thanks to Poker I've been put in rules
with some very very very big people and
the way that I make money off of this
which is not money because every single
time I go play with these guys I lose is
the network that I get because your
network is your network this is not a
stable source of income because whenever
I get a good hand every single time I
smile I laugh these guys catch on and I
lose the money right away and finally my
fifth and actually the biggest source of
income is my big big big trading account
my big trading account generates me
anywhere from a hundred fifty thousand
dollars to upwards of 250
000 every single month generating this
probably takes me about an extra minutes
a day than it already does because I
take the exact same trades that I do on
my small account I just up the lot size
on my big account so it's the same time
all I do is just takes me a little bit
more time to hop out from one account to
go to the other one and take the trade I
don't like doing an automatic I like
taking the trades manually myself
especially when you're dealing with such
big numbers and basically the way how I
accumulated this is by just showcasing
my skill set and being consistent with
it there's so many people out there that
one don't be consistent with their
trading don't showcase it and they just
don't stick to the rules I've been doing
this for five years you are destined to
be good at something if you do it every
single day for the next five years
that's where I am right now that's why I
always managed to get my big big trading
account that generates me anywhere from
150 to 200 a month building these five
sources of income has taken me five
years where I had to go from Dunkin
Donuts to working overnight shifts
working at the fair and so much more you
want to know the whole entire story on
how I did it just click this link up
here where it's my whole entire story
how I went from Duncan to the position
that I am in today however this journey
was extremely dark and long because I
didn't have a mentor to tell me what I
had to do and what I didn't have to do
so there was many highs and many lows
because nobody told me what was right my
process was full of consistent fails and
errors however all of those errors
allowed me to get these sources of
income and the good news is that if you
want to achieve the same things that I
have you don't have to go to the same
struggles if you would like to get
anywhere from a thousand to a thousand
five hundred dollars a week as a
beginner Forex Trader using a simple
strategy I have an invitation for you go
to the link in the description below
where there's a video where it explains
all you have to do is just click on it
there I explain how you can get anywhere
from a thousand to a thousand five
hundred dollars a week using a simple
Forex strategy as a beginner just like
the 500 plus success stories that I have
don't believe me just click the link
below what I have prepared for you is
going to make sense if not you can just
come to your own conclusions and I
appreciate you watching the video all
the way to the end make sure to hit that
like And subscribe button and I'll see
you guys in the next video